# CASPER PURTLEBAUGH

Hollywood, CA 805-754-8101

### SUMMARY

A full-stack web developer who is passionate about learning, clean code and problem-solving. My Philosophy degree and former IT experience have honed my ability to identify and break down problems, while being a musician allows me to approach solutions creatively. I'm pursuing a full-time role that's focused on music, entertainment, media, or marketing.

## **SKILLS**

Javascript, Angular.js, Node.js,
Express, MongoDB, RoR, Postgres,
SQL, Bootstrap, jQuery, HTML5,
CSS3, SASS, Responsive Web
Design, Grunt, Git, Heroku,
Mongolab, TravisCI, Amazon S3,
OAUTH, MVC, REST, AJAX, JSON,
API's, TDD with Mocha, Chai,
Karma, and Jasmine, Agile
Methodologies, Pivotal Tracker,
IIS7/8, Active Directory, MS
Exchange, Sketch, Adwords, Social
Media and Digital Marketing.

## **EDUCATION**

# University of California, Santa Barbara

B.A. Philosophy, 2011

#### General Assembly, DTLA

Web Development Immersive, 2015

WDI is a full-time 12 week program that focuses on technologies such as javascript, RoR, MEAN stack, etc. I spent over 600+ hours of study and completed four web projects.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Linkedin

# Full-stack Developer, Rhubarb Studios 09/2015 - Present

**Portfolio** 

Build MVP's using agile methodologies and iterative design. Utilize technologies such as Javascript, Node.js, Angular.js, Mongo, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS, Grunt, Heroku, Mongolab, and TravisCI. We pair-program daily and apply TDD. **Accomplishments:** Built a web app for Castifi, an entertainment startup from ground zero over four months. Currently building a web app for **GOBE**, a volunteer driven social-activation startup.

**Github** 

**Email** 

# Teaching Assistant, General Assembly 11/2015 - 04/2016

Assist web development immersive students with their coursework during after-hours. Technologies reviewed: Javascript, RoR, MEAN stack, Git, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Ionic.

# IT Administrator | Assistant to Office Manager, Taylor Blessey LLP 05/2013 - 05/2016

Managed the firm's network (35 users), maintained networked devices, provided desktop support and researched technical issues to implement solutions. I assisted the Office Manager with various tasks and and acted as the primary liaison with third party IT vendors. Routine duties included setting up and disconnecting networked users on Active Directory and Exchange. **Accomplishments:** Overlooked and coordinated the firm's network refresh. Served as the technical project manager for the firm's space build-out which included coordinating the server room, installation of CAT6 cabling and implementing Avaya VoIP system.

# Software Implementation, Alamar Healthcare Inc. 01/2011 - 05/2012

Implemented, migrated, and instructed staff (including senior Physicians) on EHR/PM software. Researched MU, federal regulatory compliance, and tech-oriented legal questions. Drafted proposals to regulators, procedural manuals, templates, and generated word-merge documents.

Accomplishments: Successfully passed Stage one of MU.